Burak Kaan Çopur

I hold a BS degree in CS from Bilkent University, Turkey. I worked in the defense industry for some time, looking to move into new fields. I have experience in C/C++, computer graphics, low-level programming, embedded Linux systems and some parallel programming. I was pursuing an Ms. degree at Bilkent University, specializing in computer graphics and fluid simulation. I was the TA for Parallel Programming classes for two years. My education was cut short due to not being able to pay tuition fee any longer. My registration is suspended till I pay again. Beside these, I am also interested in humans and what they achieve as a creative whole.

Technical Skills

Likes: c++ opengl cuda

Experience

R&D Engineer – AppearTV c++, vocto

 $\textit{Jan 2019} \rightarrow \textit{Current}$

Embedded Software Engineer - ASELSAN Inc.

c++, qt, linux, git

Mar 2018 → Dec 2018

I am working on an embedded IP camera software stack. This includes anything from camera module drivers to it's web based controllers. I am maintaining the middle-ware where I add new capabilities to the driver and expose them to outside world using web services. Job is using C++ and Qt mostly. Though not my thing, I occasionally fix things in the Angular front-end as well.

$\textbf{Software Engineerc} - \underline{\textbf{Cs-Tech}}$

Jan 2017 → Aug 2017

c++, qt, opengl

I worked on the company's GIS and visualization tools, using technologies like Qt, C++, OpenGL. The job mainly involved rendering engineering, computer graphics and occasional GUI programming.

Computer Science - Bilkent University

Sep 2009 → Jan 2015

Education